thirdlove.com 2018-11-17

# Privacy Policy– ThirdLove

### 

### Privacy Policy

Effective Date:  July 1, 2018

**Introduction**

Our relationship with you is very important to us. We are sensitive to protecting the private information that you provide to us. We also want you to have the opportunity to receive interesting and useful information about ThirdLove and about our products and services.

This Privacy Policy sets out how we obtain, store and use your personal information when you use or interact with www.ThirdLove.com or when we otherwise obtain or collect your personal information. By using our website or sharing your personal information with us, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

You are not required to submit any information to our website. However, without providing certain requested information, you may be unable to place an order or access certain features of our website, including Fit Finder®.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. We recommend that you print a copy of this Privacy Policy and any future versions in force from time to time for your records.

The data controller in respect of our website is ThirdLove, Inc., 555 19th Street, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA. You can contact the data controller by sending an email to privacy@ThirdLove.com.

**Collection of Information About You**

Each time a user visits our website, certain use and navigation information is collected by our servers. This information is aggregated and anonymous. It gives us information such as the number, frequency and duration of visits to each web page, which information we use to improve the content and navigation features of our website.

We also use “cookies” on our site. Cookies are small pieces of information that our server places on a visitor’s hard drive to enable that person to use our site more easily. For example, we place a cookie on your computer when you visit our site. The next time you visit our site using the same computer, our server will recognize the cookie and your personal preferences.

If you would like to opt out of accepting cookies altogether, you can generally set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. However, certain features of our website or other services may not work optimally if you delete or disable cookies.

We collect personal information about you when you provide it to us, such as through your use of our website and its features, when you contact us directly by e-mail, phone, in writing, or via social media, when you order goods and services, when you use any of our other applications, and any other means by which you provide personal information to us. The type of information we collect about you may include the following kinds of information:

  * Your name
  * Your e-mail address
  * Your postal address
  * Your phone number
  * Your payment information (e.g., your credit or debit card details)
  * Information about your computer (e.g., your IP address and browser type)
  * Information about how you use our website (e.g., which pages you have viewed, the time you viewed them and what you clicked on)
  * Information about your mobile device (such as your geographical location)

Information we obtain from third parties will generally include your name and contact details, but may include any additional information they provide to us, including some or all of the types of information set out in the list above.

We may also obtain personal information about you from certain publicly accessible sources, including (but not limited to) the electoral register, online customer databases, third-party lists and directories, media publications, social media, websites and other publicly accessible sources.

When you place an order, submit your account information, or participate in ThirdLove promotions or surveys, our website collects your personal information, such as your name, e-mail address, and mailing address. ThirdLove will use your information to process and fulfill your order. Additionally, your e-mail address may be collected at various points within the website (including when you place an order with us) so that we can send you any necessary e-mail messages related to your order, such as order and shipping confirmations.

**Use of Your Personal Information**

At ThirdLove, we understand and recognize that we must maintain and use customer information responsibly.

We maintain a record of your purchase history, product interests, and whatever other details might enable us to improve your shopping experience. Analytics such as website use and traffic patterns are also considered to help us improve the design of our website, the products we make and exclusive services we offer.

ThirdLove does not rent or sell to others your e-mail address. We do not store or share credit card information with third parties, except for the purpose of processing your order payment and as required by law.

If for any reason you choose to access a third-party website linked to our website, you do so at your own risk. We are not responsible for how these outside parties may collect, use, protect or disclose the information you provide them.

ThirdLove never stores or saves pictures taken by our sizing app. All measurement calculations take place natively on your phone.

In order to better understand our customers’ body types and preferences for particular styles, we may collect and analyze aggregated, anonymous measurement, size and shape information about our users and their purchases. The anonymous, aggregated data that we may collect could be used in a variety of ways, including but not limited to, improving the performance of our products and helping us to understand more about the relationships between body shapes, sizes and style preferences. We may also, in the future, share such aggregated, anonymous information with third-party partners. By providing your personal information to us, you are consenting to the collection and use of such anonymous, aggregated data.

**Website Statistics**

Web data is collected to monitor user trends on our website. Analytical data such as “hits” to our server, traffic patterns and page views show us where our audience is coming from and how they interact with us online. This type of collected information does not personally identify specific website users. In addition, like most websites, our website may utilize “web beacons,” “pixel tags” or other tracking technologies to help us study the actions of our users through non-personally identifiable information. This data may be aggregated with similar data collected from other users to help us to improve ThirdLove products and services and your overall website experience.

**Information Sharing with Outside Parties**

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities, such as information processing, fulfilling customer orders, lead generation, providing pre/post customer service, managing and enhancing customer and prospective customer data, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. We may also combine the personal information you provide with other personal information available from other sources. This information will then be used to enhance and personalize your shopping experience, and to make our marketing efforts more efficient. ThirdLove does not sell your personal information to third parties.

ThirdLove ensures that its third-party contracts contain proper controls for the anonymizing and encryption of personal data, breach detection, and deletion of personal data at the end of the contract term.

ThirdLove may also share your personally identifiable and/or your non-personally identifiable information, including your name, address, e-mail address, and any transactions you conduct on our website or offline with us with a third-party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver to you advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain other websites.  Our advertising partners make the data we provide anonymous.

From time to time we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe to be trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy policies are consistent with ours. We may make your name, e-mail address, and postal address available to other direct marketing companies who may have offers of interest to you. If do not wish to receive such mailings, or if you would like to opt out of ThirdLove’s direct mail and catalogs, please send an email with your full name, e-mail and postal address to [unsubscribe@thirdlove.com](https://mail.google.com/mail/?view=cm&fs=1&tf=1&to=unsubscribe@thirdlove.com) ** **

We may also share your personal information to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by ThirdLove, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; to enforce the ThirdLove Terms of Service (available separately on our website); to protect our rights; or to protect the safety of members of the public or of users of our products or services.

ThirdLove reserves the right to transfer personal information to a a third party that acquires rights to receive such information as a result of the sale of ThirdLove or substantially all of its assets to that party.

**Security**

We employ physical, electronic, and administrative safety measures to assist us in protecting your personal information and credit card data. These safeguards help us to prevent fraud and unauthorized access, as well as to maintain data accuracy. In addition, we use professionally reasonable efforts to block access to your personal information from ThirdLove employees (except those having a need to know for purposes of fulfilling your order or otherwise doing their jobs) and corporate partners to ensure your personal information is always kept safe.

**Access to Information, Correction, Deletion**

You have the right to request access to the information we have on you. You can do this by contacting us at privacy@ThirdLove.com. In response to such a request, we will provide you with a copy of the data we have about you. In order to comply with your request, we may ask you to verify your identity. We will fulfill your request by sending your copy to you electronically, unless your request expressly specifies a different method.

If you believe that the information we have about you is incorrect, you can contact us to update it. Click on the Contact link at the bottom of any ThirdLove web page for information on how to contact us.

If at any point you wish for ThirdLove to delete information about you, please submit your request to [privacy@ThirdLove.com](mailto:privacy@ThirdLove.com).

**International Privacy Laws**

If you are visiting our website from outside of the United States, please be aware that you are sending information (including personal data) to the United States, where our servers are located. That information may then be transferred within the United States or back out of the United States to other countries outside of your country of residence, depending on the type of information and how it is stored by us. These countries (including the United States) may not necessarily have data protection laws as comprehensive or protective as those in your country of residence; however, our collection, storage and use of your personal data will at all times be governed by this Privacy Policy.

**Children**

Our website is not created for or intended to be used by children, except those who have their parents’ permission. We do not believe children are interested in our site, and do not knowingly collect information from children under 18, except where a parent has authorized the release to us of information. If you are a parent or guardian and think we have unauthorized information about your child, please [contact us](https://mail.google.com/mail/?view=cm&fs=1&tf=1&to=webmaster@callawaygolf.com):  [privacy@ThirdLove.com](mailto:privacy@ThirdLove.com).

**Modification of Policy**

ThirdLove may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check back often to review any modifications that may have been made.  The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will be available at www.ThirdLove.com/privacy. By continuing to access or use our website after  changes to this Policy become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us:  [privacy@ThirdLove.com](mailto:privacy@ThirdLove.com).
